Guide to the Robert K. Merton Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Correspondence, 1930-2003
  - Subseries II.1: Alphabetical, 1930-2003
    - Kandel, Denise and Eric, 1982-2000 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Kaplan, Jeremiah, 1949-1993 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Kaplan, Joseph, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Kaplan, Justin, 1989-1990 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Katz, James E.
      - General, 1988-2000 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Caller ID Research, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Internet Use Study
        - General, 1994-2000 (Box 47, Folder 5)
        - Survey Results, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Keller, Susanne, 1953-2002 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Kelly, Robert, 1988-2003 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Kendall, Patricia L., 1943-1990, (2 Folders) (Box 47, Folder 9-10)
    - Kennedy, Randall, 1976-1996 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Kermode, Frank, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Kevles, Bettyan, 1986-1998 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Kevles, Daniel, 1964-1990 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Kikuchi, Ayako, 1972-1990 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Klausner, Samuel, 1957-1985 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Kluckhorn, Clyde, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Knopf, Alfred A., 1961-1983 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Komarovsky, Mirra, 1945-1999 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Kracauer, Siegfried, 1966-1968, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Kruskal, William, 1963-1991, (2 Folders) (Box 48, Folder 8-9)
    - Kyoto American Studies Summer Seminar, 1967-1975 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - L--General
      - LA, 1944-2001 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - LA, 1944-2001, (2 Folders) (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
      - LE, 1946-2003, (4 Folders) (Box 49, Folder 3-6)
      - LI-End, 1937-2002, (3 Folders) (Box 49, Folder 7-9)
      - LI-End, 1937-2002, (4 Folders) (Box 50, Folder 1-4)
    - Lakatos, Imre, 1971-1976 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Lammers, Cornelis, 1964-1992 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Lamo, Emilio, 1999-2001 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Larsen, Otto, 1966-1994 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Lawrence, Charles
      - General, 1942-1951 (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - Memorial Lecture, 1997-2001 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - LeBlanc, Janette, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Lécuyer, Bernard-Pierre, 1973-1998, (2 Folders) (Box 50, Folder 12-13)
    - Lécuyer, Bernard-Pierre, 1978 (Box 150, Folder 18)
    - Lederberg, Joshua
      - General, 1972-2000, (5 Folders) (Box 51, Folder 1-5)
      - Columbia University Honorary Degree Nomination, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Institutional Bases of Translation in the Twelfth Century, 1981-1987 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - National Medal of Science, 1971-1984 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Lee, Jennifer, 1993-2001, (2 Folders) (Box 52, Folder 1-2)
    - Lee, Ronnal, 1968-1981 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Lee, T.D., 1986-1993 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Lemann, Nicholas, 1991-2001 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Lennard, Henry, 1959-1980 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Lenzer, Gertrud, 1997-1998 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Lepenies, Wolf, 1972-1996, (2 Folders) (Box 52, Folder 8-9)
    - Lepenies, Wolf, 1984 (Box 251, Folder 19)
    - Lerner, Daniel, 1948-1950 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Levine, Donald
      - General, 1969-1998, (2 Folders) (Box 52, Folder 11-12)
      - "Social Theory as a Vocation," 1997 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Levine, Gene, 1956-1964, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Lewis, Richard, 1970-1975 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Lilley, S., 1947-1951 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Lindblom, Charles, 1979-1995 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Lindt, Gillian, 1969-2002 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Linton, Ralph, 1938-1940 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Linz, Juan
      - General, 1956-1971 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Festschrift, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Lipset, Seymour Martin
      - General, 1946-2000, (3 Folders) (Box 53, Folder 10-12)
      - American Professoriate Study and Questionnaire, 1971-1981 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - Festschrift, 1990-1995 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Memoir, 1945, 1991-2002 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Litwak, Eugene, 1951-1992 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Logan, John, 1997-1998 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Loomis, Charles, 1943-1963 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Lorch, Maristella, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Lowenthal, Leo, 1943-1958 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Lynd, Helen, 1956-1980 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Lynd, Robert, 1943-1980, (2 Folders) (Box 54, Folder 9-10)
    - M--General
      - M-MAZ, 1935-2002 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - M-MAZ, 1935-2002, (3 Folders) (Box 55, Folder 1-3)
      - MAC, MC, 1948-2002, (4 Folders) (Box 55, Folder 4-7)
      - ME-MIL, 1940-2002, (4 Folders) (Box 56, Folder 1-4)
      - MIM-MOO, 1948-1999, (3 Folders) (Box 56, Folder 5-7)
      - MOR-End, 1932-2002, (3 Folders) (Box 57, Folder 1-3)
    - Macaulay, Stewart, 1961-1995 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Marcson, Simon, 1943-1945, 1961-1980 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Marías, Julián, 1986-1999 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Marks, Paul, 1971-1999 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Marshall, James, 1954-1970 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Marx, Gary, 1980-1994 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Mass Persuasion Republication, 2001-2002 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Mayntz, Renate, 1959-1964 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Mayr, Ernst, 1975-2002 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - McDonald, Lavern, 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - McGill, William, 1970-1980 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - McPhee, William, 1959-1968 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - McSweeney, Anne, 1984-1987 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Medawar, Peter, 1978-1986 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Miles, Mary, 1970-1990 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Miller, Arthur, 1938-1957, 1979-1981 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Mills, Kate (Wright), 1996-2000, (2 Folders) (Box 58, Folder 9-10)
    - Mitchell, Douglas, 1978-2002, (3 Folders) (Box 58, Folder 11-13)
    - Mitroff, Ian, 1972-1977 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Mongardini, Carlo, 1987-2000 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Mongardini, Joannes, 1989-2002 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Montagu, Ashley, 1938-1954, 1975-1984, (2 Folders) (Box 59, Folder 4-5)
    - Moore, Wilbert E., 1940-1951, 1968, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Morawska, Ewa, 1985-1996 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Movia, Giovanna, 1989-1997 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Moton Center for Independent Studies, 1974-1976 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, 1992-1998 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Muller, Jerry, 1995-1997 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Mullinix, Kathleen, 1985-1993 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Mullins, Nicholas, 1972-1987 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - N--General
      - NA-NEU, 1944-1999, (3 Folders) (Box 60, Folder 1-3)
      - NEW-End, 1944-2000, (3 Folders) (Box 60, Folder 4-6)
    - National Academy of Education, 1965-2001 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - National Academy of Sciences
      - General, 1959, 1986-1997 (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - Committees
        - Behavioral Science, 1952-1984 (Box 60, Folder 9)
        - History and Philosophy of Science, 1975-1976 (Box 60, Folder 10)
        - Human Rights, 1972-1996 (Box 61, Folder 1)
        - Science and Public Policy, 1969-1976 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Institute of Medicine, 1973-1995 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - James Murray Luck Award, 1978-1981 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - National Research Council
        - General, 1968-1986 (Box 61, Folder 5)
        - Assembly of Behavioral and Social Sciences, 1975-1977 (Box 61, Folder 6)
        - History of Science and Technology, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 7)
        - Study of Advisory Services to Government, 1969-1973 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Nominations, 1970-1977 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - Personal Membership Election, 1968-1972 (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - Section Members, 1976-1978, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - "Sharing Research Data," 1982 (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - Temporary Nominating Group, 1974-1976 (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - Working Group on U.S.-U.S.S.R. Systems for Fundamental Research, 1973-1975 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - National Medal of Science, 1994-1996 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - National Science Foundation, 1949-1993, (2 Folders) (Box 61, Folder 16-17)
    - National Urban League, 1975-1979 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - The Natural Philosopher, 1962-1965 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Nee, Victor, 1995-2000 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Needham, Joseph, 1938, 1974, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Nelson, Benjamin, 1962-1977 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Neurath, Paul (Director of Paul Lazarsfeld Archive), 1962-2000, (3 Folders) (Box 62, Folder 6-8)
    - New School for Social Research, 1981-1984 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - New York Academy of Sciences, 1985-1997 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - New York Society of Fellows, 1987-1988 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - New York State Sociological Association, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - New York Times
      - Book Reviews, 1991-1994 (Box 62, Folder 13)
      - Magazine, 1961-1962 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Nichols, Lawrence, 1976-1998 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Nichols, Lawrence, 1997 (Box 251, Folder 6)
    - Nisbet, Robert, 1947-1996 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Nitze, Paul H., 1974 (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - Noelle-Neumann, Elisabeth, 1988-1999 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Nordmann, Alfred, 1986-2000 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Nugayev, Rinat, 1989-1999 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - O--General, 1943-2001, (2 Folders) (Box 63, Folder 3-4)
    - Oberlin College, 1962-1973 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Oberschall, Anthony, 1972-1978, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Odum, Howard, 1940-1941 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Office of Science and Technology Development, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - O’Gorman, Hubert, 1961-1990 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Olson, Mancur, 1971-1994 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Opp, Karl-Dieter, 1970-1999 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Orrù, Marco, 1985-1994 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - P--General
      - PA-PE, 1955-2000, (2 Folders) (Box 63, Folder 13-14)
      - PE-PL, 1952-2002, (2 Folders) (Box 64, Folder 1-2)
      - PO-End, 1940-2000, (3 Folders) (Box 64, Folder 3-5)
    - Pacific Lutheran University, 1995-1997 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Page, Charles, 1949-1996 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Papper, E.M., 1998 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Parsons, Anne, 1957, undated (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Parsons, Talcott
      - General, 1936-1976, (4 Folders) (Box 65, Folder 1-4)
      - Items Regarding, 1973-1998 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Tributes, 1973-1989 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - University of Heidelberg Conference, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Participation Refusals, 1948-1998, (4 Folders) (Box 65, Folder 8-11)
    - Participation Refusals, 1948-1998, (8 Folders) (Box 66, Folder 1-8)
    - Participation Refusals, 1948-1998, (2 Folders) (Box 67, Folder 1-2)
    - Pasanella, Ann, 1963-1996, (2 Folders) (Box 67, Folder 3-4)
    - Passas, Nikos, 1986-2001 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Patinkin, Donald, 1980-1991 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Patel, Pravin, 1983-1999 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Pending, 2000-2003, (2 Folders) (Box 349, Folder 1-2)
    - Petersen, William, 1950-1958 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Peyre, Henri, 1962-1964 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Philipson, Morris, 1960, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Photograph Requests and Permissions, 1964-1985 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Piel, Gerald, 1963-2001, (3 Folders) (Box 68, Folder 1-3)
    - Platt, Jennifer, 1981-1993 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Podgorecki, Adam, 1967- 1998 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Pokrovsky, Nikita, 1990-2000 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Polanyi, Karl, 1947-1963 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Polanyi, Michael, 1969-1977 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Polish Academy of Sciences, 1997-1998 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Pollack, Robert, 1983-1999 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Polsky, Ned, 1956-1999 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Portes, Alejandro, 1993-2002 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Price, Derek de Solla, 1960-1986 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Price, James L., 1957-1969 (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Prince, Ivin, 1973-1991 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - The Public Opinion Quarterly, 1985-1988 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Pyenson, Lewis, 1973, 1990-1998 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Quartet--Alfred Cohn, Edward R. Murrow, and Harold Laski, 1942-1963, 1984-1992 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - R--General, 1939-2002, (3 Folders) (Box 69, Folder 8-10)
    - R--General, 1939-2002, (9 Folders) (Box 70, Folder 1-9)
    - Ramsøy, Natalie Rogoff, 1959-1994 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Rand Corporation, 1949, 1954, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Rango, Nicholas, 1977-1986 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Ray, Gordon, 1964-1985 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Reader, George, 1955-1993 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Reed, John S., 1972-2001 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Referee Reports, 1971-1977 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Reisman, David, 1947-1961 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Reismann, Frank, Jr., 1948-1948 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Riecken, Henry, 1939-1941, 1963-1972 (Box 71, Folder 8-10)
    - Riesman, David, 1947-1996 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Riley, Jack and Matilda, 1950-2001, (3 Folders) (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Riley, Jack and Matilda, 1950-2001, (4 Folders) (Box 72, Folder 1-4)
    - Rogers, Everett, 1991-1995 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Rose, Daniel, 1993-2002 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Rose, Peter I., 1967-1992 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Rosenblatt, Aaron, 1979-2002, (2 Folders) (Box 72, Folder 8-9)
    - Rosenfeld, Eva, 1946-1994 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Rossi, Alice, 1949-1963, 1982-1999 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Rossi, Alice, 1951 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Rossi, Peter, 1949-1994 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Rothman, David, 1982-1992 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - The Royal Swedish Academy of Sciences, 1975-2000
      - General, 1975-2000 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Social Mechanisms Conference, 1994-1996 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Rudenstine, Neil, 1989-1991 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - S--General
      - SA-SCA, 1943-2001, (2 Folders) (Box 73, Folder 8-9)
      - SCH, 1941-2002, (2 Folders) (Box 73, Folder 10-11)
      - SCH, 1941-2002, (1 Folders) (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - SCI-SE, 1947, 1960-1997, (2 Folders) (Box 74, Folder 2-3)
      - SH, 1954-2002, (3 Folders) (Box 74, Folder 4-6)
      - SI-SN, 1938-2001, (2 Folders) (Box 74, Folder 7-8)
      - SI-SN, 1938-2001, (2 Folders) (Box 75, Folder 1-2)
      - SO-STE, 1940-2001, (4 Folders) (Box 75, Folder 3-6)
      - STI-End, 1942-2002, (1 Folders) (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - STI-End, 1942-2002, (2 Folders) (Box 76, Folder 1-2)
    - Sackler, Arthur, 1985-1986 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Safire, William, undated (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Sagarin, Edward, 1973-1996 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - The Salk Institute, 1974-1980 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Sammer, Jan, 1988-1989 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Samuelson, Paul, 1974-2001, (3 Folders) (Box 76, Folder 8-10)
    - Sarton, George
      - General, 1996-1999 (Box 76, Folder 11)
      - ISIS Publications
        - General, 1949-1950, 1974-1985 (Box 76, Folder 12)
        - Responses to, 1986 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - University of Ghent--Chair, 1984-1986 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Sarton, May
      - General, 1940, 1962-1997, (2 Folders) (Box 77, Folder 3-4)
      - The Sarton Fund, 1996 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Schneider, Louis
      - General, 1942-1987, (3 Folders) (Box 77, Folder 6-8)
      - With Irwin Primer, 1972-1978 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Schrank, Harris, 1983-1999 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Schuler, Edgar,1943-1957 1978-1980, 1998 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Science the Endless Frontier Conference, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Science Magazine Reviews, 1964-1978 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Scientific American, 1986-1987 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Scott, Lise and Ron, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Self Emancipation Proclamation, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Selvin, Hanan, 1950-1994, (2 Folders) (Box 78, Folder 7-8)
    - Selznick, Philip, 1941-1995 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Shafer, Byron, 1979-2000, (4 Folders) (Box 78, Folder 10-13)
    - Shafer, Byron, 1979-2000, (2 Folders) (Box 79, Folder 1-2)
    - Shafer, Byron, 1983-1997, (2 Folders) (Box 251, Folder 7-8)
    - Shalin, Dmitri, 1990 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Shils, Edward, 1940, 1962-2001 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Shulman, James, 1997-2002 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Shulman, Lee, 1977-1984 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Sica, Alan
      - General, 1985-2002, (4 Folders) (Box 79, Folder 7-10)
      - General, 1985-2002, (4 Folders) (Box 80, Folder 1-4)
      - Incoming, 1984-1996, (2 Folders) (Box 80, Folder 5-6)
      - Outgoing, 1985-2002, (2 Folders) (Box 80, Folder 7-8)
    - Sills, David
      - General, 1962-2002, (7 Folders) (Box 81, Folder 1-7)
      - General, 1962-2002, (2 Folders) (Box 82, Folder 1-2)
      - Distinguished Career Award, American Sociological Association, 1986-1987 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Social Science Quotations, 1995-1998 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Silver, Allan, 1967-1984 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Silverstein, Theodore, 1938-1954, 1990-2001, undated (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Simonson, Peter, 1999-2003 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Simpson, George, 1936-1954, 1971-1999, (2 Folders) (Box 82, Folder 8-9)
    - Simpson, Richard, 1994-1996 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Singer, Burton, 1976-1989 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Singer, Eleanor, 1982-1999 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Skolnick, Jerome, 1982-1996 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Sloan Foundation, 1994-1999 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research, 1965, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Smelsner, Neil, 1970-2002 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Smith, Charles E., 1985-2000 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Smith, Robert, 1974-2001, (2 Folders) (Box 83, Folder 8-9)
    - The Snark, 1995-1996 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Snizek, William, 1975-2002 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Social Science Quotations, 1992-1990 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Social Science Research Council
      - General, 1975-1998 (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - Committee on History and Sociology of Science, 1956-1968 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Social Sciences at MIT, 1988-1991 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Sociological Visions, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Sociology of Science--Korean Translation, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Sociology Today, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Sofronieva, Tsveta, 1988-1990 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Solís, Carlos, 1996-1998 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Solow, Robert, 1987-2000 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Somers, Robert, 1963-1969, 1989-1999 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Sorokin and Civilization: A Centennial Assessment, 1974-1991 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Sorokin, Pitirim
      - General, 1930-1964, (2 Folders) (Box 102, Folder 2-3)
      - American Sociological Association, 1962-1963 (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - Festschrifts, 1959-1962 (Box 102, Folder 5)
      - Harvard Communist Newsletter, 1935-1936 (Access Copies) (Box 102, Folder 6)
      - Harvard Communist Newsletter, 1936 (Box 102, Folder 7)
        [Restricted]
      - Sociology of Revolution, 1966-1968, 1999 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Sovern, Michael, 1973-1992, (3 Folders) (Box 84, Folder 14-16)
    - Spiegel, Herbert, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Srole, Leo, 1940-1997, (3 Folders) (Box 85, Folder 2-4)
    - Stafford, Becky, 1977-1980 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Stanton, Frank, 1957-2001 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Statera, Gianni, 1969-1985 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Stehr, Nico, 1979-2002, (3 Folders) (Box 85, Folder 8-10)
    - Stehr, Nico, 1975-1984, (2 Folders) (Box 349, Folder 3-4)
    - Stein, Clarence, 1946-1947 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Stein, Maurice, 1951-1958 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Stent, Gunther, 1971-1990 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Stern, Bernhard, 1938-1961 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Stern, Carl, 1945-1955 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Stern Family Fund, 1959-1961 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Stern, Fritz, 1973-2000 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Stigler, George, 1969-1998 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Stigler, Stephen, 1972-2002, (3 Folders) (Box 86, Folder 9-11)
    - Stigler, Stephen, 1972-2002, (6 Folders) (Box 87, Folder 1-6)
    - Stinchcombe, Arthur, 1962-1999 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Stinchcombe, Arthur, 1973-1975 (Box 251, Folder 9)
    - Storer, Norman, 1961-1991 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Sussmann, Leila, 1945-1971, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Sutherland, Edwin H., Award Lecture, 1996-1997 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Swain, Carol, 1993-1994 (Box 251, Folder 10)
    - Swedberg, Richard, 1975-2002 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Sweezy, Paul, 1950-1951 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Swiss Institute for Development--Anomie Research Group, 1994-1998 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Szalai, Alexander, 1977-1981 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Sztompka, Piotr, 1974-2002, (5 Folders) (Box 89, Folder 1-5)
    - T--General, 1939-2002, (2 Folders) (Box 89, Folder 6-7)
    - T--General, 1939-2002, (4 Folders) (Box 90, Folder 1-4)
    - Tabboni, Simonetta, 1985-2002 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Tavistock Institute, 1948-1949 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Tavuchis, Nick, 1978-1996 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Tawil, Ellen, 1993-1996 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Taylor, Carl, 1994-1996 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Tec, Nechama, 1973-1994 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Temple University, 1956, 1963, 1980-1998 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Thackray, Arnold, 1969-2000, (5 Folders) (Box 91, Folder 3-7)
    - Theory and Society, 1973-1984 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Thomas, Dorothy Swaine, 1973-1996 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Thomas, Dorothy Swaine, 1952-1973 (Box 251, Folder 11)
    - "The Thomas Theorem and The Matthew Effect" Responses, 1994-1996 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Time Magazine, 1949 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Tiryakian, Edward, 1979-2002, (2 Folders) (Box 92, Folder 3-4)
    - Toby, Jackson, 1950-1951, 1970-1988 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Tootell, Geoffrey, 1969-2002 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Toward a Metric of Science, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Transaction Publications, 1991-1999 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Trilling, Diana and Lionel, 1965-1996 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Trimble, Virginia, 1993-2002 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Trow, Martin, 1949-1950 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Truzzi, Marcello, 1967-1986 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Tufte, Edward, 1974-2002, (2 Folders) (Box 93, Folder 2-3)
    - Tumin, Melvin, 1948-1976 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - U--General, 1961-1997 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Unidentified Correspondents, 1992-2002 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - United Nations, 1969, 1980-1981 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO), 1948-1976 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - United Negro College Fund, 1964-1965 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - University Center in Virginia, Inc., 1958-1970 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - University Loyalty Oath, 1950-1952, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - University of Bologna, 1986-1988 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - University of Bombay
      - General, 1968-1970 (Box 93, Folder 13)
      - Dissertations, 1954-1971 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - University of Chicago Press, 1973-1998 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Unnithan, Narayanan, 1971-1994 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - V--General, 1946-2002, (2 Folders) (Box 94, Folder 1-2)
    - van Dalen, Hendrik, 1995-1998 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - van den Belt, Henk, 1996-1997 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - The Van Leer Jerusalem Foundation
      - Advisory Board on Publications, 1971-1978, 1993 (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - History of Science Conference, 1970-1971 (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - Traveling Colloquium, 1971 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Van Toor, James, 1946 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - Varma, Baidya Nath, 1961-1998, (3 Folders) (Box 94, Folder 8-10)
    - Vaughan, Diane, 1986-1999 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Vaughan, Samuel, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - W--General
      - WA-WAS, 1947-2000, (3 Folders) (Box 95, Folder 1-3)
      - WAT-WEI, 1930, 1956-2002, (3 Folders) (Box 95, Folder 4-6)
      - WEL-WH, 1943-1999, (3 Folders) (Box 95, Folder 7-9)
      - WI, 1938-2002, (4 Folders) (Box 96, Folder 1-4)
      - WO-End, 1943-2002, (3 Folders) (Box 96, Folder 5-7)
    - Wacquant, Loїc, 1988-2002, (2 Folders) (Box 96, Folder 8-9)
    - Waldrip, Ceil Cleveland, 1978-1983 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Wallace, Walter, 1970-2000 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Wallis, Allen, 1955-1979 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Wallner, Mathias, 1988-1989 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Wanner, Eric, 1985-2001, (2 Folders) (Box 97, Folder 5-6)
    - Warren, Kenneth, 1991-1992 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Warsh, David, 1996-2002 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - The Washington Post, 1995 (Box 97, Folder 9)